Did you come here to see it too?
Huh?
Look.  There's a big mountain over the sea, right?
You're right.
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
Ichinichi no hajimari to
１日の始まりと
From the start of the day
（はるか）あなたも見に来たの？
（純一）えッ？
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
終わりにはいつも傍に
Till the end, you're by my side
ほら　あの海の向こうに
おっきい山が見えるでしょ？
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
あなたがいる　そんな毎日
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
目を覚ませば温かい
When I opened my eyes
本当だ
Koohii irete matteru
コーヒー入れて待ってる
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
あなたの左腕に抱きついた
And so I clung onto your left arm
・～
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
会える日まで指折り数えていた
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
今じゃ会えない日の方が少ないね
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
こんな幸せ誰が予想した
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
あなたと私がそう
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
恋をした
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
愛してる　あなたのこと
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
初めてのキモチよ
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
愛してる　ずっとずっと
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
変わらないキモチ
My feelings will never change
・（美也）お兄ちゃん　何してんの？
Onii-chan, what are you doing?
Miya, Rihoko.
美也　梨穂子
I'm not really doing anything right now.
いや　別に何もしてないよ
（美也）ホント？
何か　キョロキョロして怪しかったよ
Really?
You look kinda suspicious, staring around like that.
（梨穂子）ねえ
これから美也ちゃんと
Hey.
Miya-chan and I are about to go shopping.
買い物に行くんだけど
純一も一緒に行かない？
Junichi, would you like to come with us?
What are you shopping for?
何　買いにいくんだ？
にしし
クリスマスセールでバーゲンやってるから
They're having a Christmas sale, so we're gonna see if there are any good deals.
掘り出し物を探しにいくんだ
ウインド－・ショッピングかな？
Window shopping, I guess.
I see.
〈なるほどね　今日は
森島先輩と一緒に帰るのは〉
I guess I'll give up on walking home with Morishima-senpai for today.
〈あきらめるか…〉
いいよ　つきあうよ
やったーッ
Sure, I'll go with you.
Yay!
梨穂ちゃん
これで荷物持ち　ゲットだね
Riho-chan, now we have someone to carry our bags!
うんって…　え～ッ？
Yeah!
Wait, I feel bad about making Junichi carry everything!
純一に全部　持たせたら悪いよ
ほどほどにしてくれよ
はいはい
Don't work me too hard.
Yeah, yeah!
じゃあ　にぃにの気が
変わらないうちに早く行こう！
Well, let's go before Nii-nii changes his mind!
ああ　美也ちゃん
そんなに急がなくても→
Miya-chan, you don't have to rush-
わあ～！
・（美也）・～ショッ　ショッショ　ショ～
ショッピング　ショッピング
Sh-Sh-Sh-Sho, shopping~
Sign: Shopping District
もう
すっかりクリスマスモードだな
Wow, you're totally in Christmas Mode, aren't you?
Yeah.  It's almost Christmas, isn't it?
・（梨穂子）そうだね
もうすぐクリスマスだからね
・（美也）あ～あ　にぃには
今年も寂しいクリスマスか
Aww, is Nii-nii gonna have another lonely Christmas?
こッ　今年は僕だって…
T-This year, I'll...
・（美也）あッ　梨穂ちゃん　あれ
見て見て
Riho-chan, look, look!
・（梨穂子）えッ　どれどれ？
What, what?
I'd rather have a chocolate cake...
〈もうすぐクリスマスだ〉
It's almost Christmas.
I need to ask her out soon.
〈早く約束をしないと…〉
〈今年のクリスマスは
森島先輩とハッピーに過ごすんだ！〉
I'm gonna spend this Christmas happily with Morishima-senpai!
えッ？
Morishima-senpai?
森島先輩？
・（梨穂子）純一　どうしたの？
Junichi, what's the matter?
Um... uh, I...
うん　えーと　その…
Nii-nii?
にぃに？
あッ　ああ…
あッ？　「あ」が　どうしたの？
"Ah"?  What do you mean, "ah"?
分かった！　にぃに
トイレに行きたいんでしょ？
I know!
Nii-nii, you need to go to the bathroom, right?
Geez, you should've just said so earlier!
・（梨穂子）もう　ヤダ～
だったら早く言えばいいのに
ほら　早く行ってきなよ
Come on, hurry up and go.
そうだよ　我慢は体に悪いよ
Yeah, it's not good for you to hold it in.
あッ　うん　じゃあ…
All right, I'll go.
先に帰ってていいから！
You can go home first if you want!
ああ…
キレイなお姉さん
僕をここから出してクマ
Pretty girl, I can't bear to stay in here any longer!
（はるか）ええ～ッ！
うわッ
橘君
Tachibana-kun?
ははは　驚きました？
Did I scare you?
Geez, you really surprised me.
もう　びっくりしちゃったじゃない
ワオ　やったーッ
クマちゃん　ゲット！
Wow, I did it!  Teddy bear, get!
Morishima Haruka Arc
Final Chapter
Romance
よかったですね
うん
That's good.
Yep.
君が脅かしてくれたおかげで
偶然　取れちゃった　ありがと！
I only happened to win because you surprised me.
Thanks!
〈森島先輩　かわいいな〉
Morishima-senpai's... really cute.
ねえ　今　時間ある？
Hey, are you free right now?
Yes, I am.
はい　大丈夫ですよ
じゃあ　ここで少し
遊んでいこっか？→
Well then, let's go have some fun over there.
あッ　でも私あんまり
ゲームセンターって来たことないの
Ah, but I don't really go to arcades often.
何か　２人でできるゲームって
ないかな？
I wonder if they have any two-player games?
う～ん…　おッ
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
We input our initials here...
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
ここにイニシャルを入れて　と…
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
Love
Fortune
Cupid
何これ
いいの　悪いの？
What's this mean?
Is it good or bad?
ああ　そうですね　すごく悪いです
Ah, let's see.
It's really bad.
うんん…
〈先輩　僕と相性が　よくないって
出て　不機嫌になるなんて〉
Senpai's all unhappy because it says we're not very compatible.
Does this mean that she likes me?
〈それだけ
思われてるってことかな？〉
I'm kinda happy.
〈ちょっと　うれしいかも〉
One more time.
もいっかいやる
えッ？　もう一度やっても
Huh?  We'll probably get the same result even if we go again...
結果は同じだと思いますけど
じゃあ　もう一度
先輩のイニシャルを入れてください
Anyway, input your initials again, Senpai.
先輩　Ｈ．Ｍじゃないんですか？
Senpai, aren't your initials H.M.?
これでいいの
は　はい…
This is fine.
O-Okay...
What's with the "L"?
〈Ｌって何だろうな？〉
うわッ　すごい！
やったーッ　大成功ね
Whoa, amazing!
We did it!  Huge success!
ふふふ　スッキリしたわ
That was satisfying!
What's with the "L", though?
でも「Ｌ」って何ですか？
先輩は森島だから「Ｍ」なんじゃ…
Shouldn't it be "M", for Morishima...?
Ｌはね　ラブリーのＬ
The "L" stands for "Lovely".
Tachibana-kun, I don't think I've told you yet.
橘君には
まだ話したこと　なかったね
私の本名は森島・ラブリー・はるかなの
My actual name is Morishima Lovely Haruka.
ラブリーはミドルネームってやつね
Lovely is my middle name.
Compatibility Fortune-Telling
What?  So you're actually half-Caucasian?
A-type
Blood Type
Blood-type
Fortune-Telling
ええ？　先輩ってハーフなんですか
ううん　えっとね
母方のおじいちゃんがイギリス人で
Compatibility Fortune-Telling
Nope.
Let's see.  My grandpa on my mother's side is English, and my grandma is Japanese.
おばあちゃんが日本人なの
So I guess that makes me quarter-Caucasian.
だから　私はクオーターってことね
I-I see.  So that's why.
なッ　なるほど
そうだったんですか
What am I saying?  I need to ask Senpai out for Christmas!
〈そうじゃなくて
先輩をクリスマスに誘わなくちゃ〉
Ahh, I feel great.  Let's go home.
Taiko
さて　スッキリしたし帰ろっか
Senpai.
先輩
おッ？
Signs: 12 Constellation - Compatibility Fortune-Telling.
Could you come with me?
今度は
僕に　つきあってくれませんか？
（はるか）珍しいわね　君が
こんなふうに誘ってくれるなんて
How rare of you to ask me like that.
先輩　寒くないですか？
Senpai, are you cold?
（はるか）ううん　大丈夫だよ→
Nope, I'm fine.
ここに来るの　久しぶり→
It's been so long since I was here.
昔は毎日　来てたのよ
I used to come here every day.
今日は見えないですね
うん？
We can't really see it today.
覚えてますか？　実は僕
Don't you remember?
We've met here before, in the past.
昔　ここで
先輩に会ったことがあるんです
１年前のあのときも
I think the sun was also setting a year ago, just like this.
ちょうど
こんな夕暮れだったと思います
《（はるか）ほら　あの海の向こうに
おっきい山が見えるでしょ？》
Look.  There's a big mountain over the sea, right?
《本当だ　あんなところに山が…》
You're right.  There's actually a mountain there...
《（はるか）天気がいい日は海の
向こうの景色がよく見えるのよ》
You can see far out into the sea when the weather's fine.
I guess so.  I didn't notice at all.
《そうだったんですね》
《全然　気づきませんでした》
《やっぱり似てる》
You really are just like him.
I'm just like someone?
《僕　誰かに似てるんですか？》
《あのね　うちで飼っていた犬に
よく似てるの》
You know, you're just like the dog we used to have.
A... dog?
《犬…　ですか？》
Especially when you have that perplexed look.
《そんな困ったような顔が特にね》
《ふふ　ごめんなさい》
Sorry.
《ははッ　そうなんですか》
Really?
《ふふふ》
《ははは…》
I was feeling pretty down at the time,
あのとき　僕は落ち込んでて
but I felt a lot better after you talked to me.
でも　声をかけてもらったおかげで
何だか楽になったんです
それから少しして　あのときの人が
うちの学校にいるって知って
A little later, I was pretty surprised to find out you were in the same school as me.
驚いたんですよ
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute.
じゃあ
橘君が　あの公園君だったの？
So Tachibana-kun, that means you're Park-kun?
えッ　公園君？
Park-kun?
You know, that day left a deep impression on me.
あのね　私　あの日のことは
印象深くて
おもしろい子に会ったって
人に話すときにね
So when I talked to people about the interesting guy I'd met,
名前が分からなかったから
公園君って
I would call him "Park-kun" because I didn't know his name.
勝手に名前をつけてたの
それが君だったのね！？
And you're actually him!
あッ　なるほど
I see.
そうです　僕が公園君です
That's right, I'm Park-kun.
There's a good reason why I went to the park that day.
私があの日
この公園に来ていたのには
ちゃんと意味があってね
John, the dog we've had since I was three, died on Christmas the year before.
３歳の頃から飼っていた
犬のジョンが
１年前のクリスマスに死んじゃって
それから思い出すたび
悲しくなって…
Since then, I'd feel sad whenever I thought of him.
でも　このままじゃ天国のジョンも
きっと私のことが心配で
But I realized that John would continue to worry about me in heaven if I stayed that way.
安心できないだろうなって
思ったの→
だからジョンが好きだった
この公園に来て→
So I decided to go to the park John had liked and cheer up.
元気出さなきゃって…→
そしたらジョンが大好きだった
このベンチに→
Then I saw this guy sitting at the bench that John had loved.
座ってる男の子がいるじゃない
それが僕だったってわけですね？
（はるか）そう→
That was me, wasn't it?
Yep.
ジョンが　しょんぼりしてたときと
同じ感じで座ってたの→
John would sit just like that whenever he was feeling down.
それで何だか　ほっとけなくて…
And so I couldn't just ignore you...
そうだったんですか
うん
So that's how it was.
Yep.
きっとジョンが橘君と私を
会わせてくれたのね
I'm sure that John brought us together.
ねえ　あのとき
何で橘君は落ち込んでたの？
Hey Tachibana-kun, why were you down at the time?
I was waiting for someone at this park on Christmas two years ago.
僕は２年前のクリスマスに　この公園で
待ち合わせをしていたんです
へえ　それって女の子？
For a girl?
橘君も意外とやるわね
Not bad at all, Tachibana-kun.
But... she stood me up.
でも　すっぽかされちゃいました
えッ
それから１年間
ずっとクヨクヨしてて
For the next year, I was constantly brooding over it.
That was what I was thinking about when I was feeling down in this park last year.
あのときも　この公園で
そのことを思い出して
落ち込んでたんです
あのとき
先輩に声をかけてもらって
Senpai, you saved me when you talked to me then.
僕は救われました
また僕を救ってくれませんか？
Could you save me again?
えッ　何？
How?
Christmas Eve, on the 24th.  Please go on a date with me.
２４日のクリスマスイブ
僕とデートしてください
I can't.
（はるか）ダメ
Y-You can't?
ダッ　ダメですか
僕とデートとかイヤですか？
Y-You don't want to go on a date with me?
（はるか）ううん　違うの→
No, that's not it.
クリスマスは毎年　イギリスから
My grandpa and grandma from England come back
each year for Christmas, and we have a party at our home.
おじいちゃんと
おばあちゃんが来て
家族でパーティーしてるの
だから…
So...
I see.  That's why.
なるほど…　そうなんですか
ふふッ　ねえ
Hey.  Will you come to the party if I invite you, Tachibana-kun?
うちのパーティーに橘君をご招待したら
来てくれるかな？
えッ？
If you're fine with that, let's spend Christmas Eve together.
もし　それでいいなら
クリスマスイブを一緒に過ごそう
はいッ　喜んで！
Yes, I'd be glad to!
ふふふ…
はあ　はあ　はあ…
〈ヤバイ
待ち合わせに完全に遅刻だ！〉
Crap, I'm totally not gonna make it!
〈美也がヘンなこと言うから！〉
It's all because Miya said something weird!
はあ　はあ…
Where could Senpai be?  Did she go back already?
〈先輩　どこだろう？
もう帰っちゃったんじゃ…〉
Hey.
・（はるか）こら！
You're a bad boy for making a girl wait on a day like this.
こんな日に女の子を待たすなんて
いけない子ね
あッ　すッ　すみません！
S-Sorry!
Oh no, Tachibana-kun.  Steam's coming out of your head!
ヤダ　橘君　頭から湯気が出てるよ
えッ…
あははは
必死に走ってきたんで
I ran really hard coming here.
Geez, you're hopeless.
もう　しょうがないんだから
I can't get mad at you if you ran hard enough to make steam come out.
こんな湯気まで出されちゃったら
怒れないじゃない
T-Thank you.
あッ　ありがとうございます
Well, let's get moving.
さッ　それじゃあ行きましょう
えッ　あ　あの…
U-Um...
Where are we going?
これから
どこに行くんでしたっけ？
先輩のおうちですか？
To your house?
ここって…　ホテルですよね？
うん
I-Isn't this...
A hotel?
Yeah.
What are we doing at a hotel?
ホテルで何をするんですか？
I'm happy that you ran so hard for me,
頑張って走って来てくれたのは
うれしいけど
汗臭いボーイフレンドを
家族に紹介できないじゃない？
but I can't introduce a sweaty boyfriend to my family, right?
So let's wash off your sweat here.
だから
ここで一汗流していきましょ
え～ッ！
What?!
What's wrong, all of a sudden?
いきなりどうしたの？
Wow.  Is it really okay to go to a hotel on the very first date?
〈そんな　初デートなのに　いきなり
ホテルとか　いいのか？〉
あの…　先輩は　いいんですか？
Well... Senpai, are you sure about this?
えっと…　何が？
Um... about what?
〈水着のレンタルがあって助かった〉
I'm so glad they rented out swimsuits.
〈まさか　ホテルのプールで
汗を流すなんて〉
I didn't expect her to mean washing off my sweat at the hotel pool...
〈しかし　プールか〉
Though... the pool, huh?
〈また
森島先輩の水着姿が拝めるぞ〉
I'll get to check out Morishima-senpai in a swimsuit again!
・（はるか）お～またせ～
Sorry I took so long!
Y-Yes!
はッ　はい！
It's a new swimsuit...
新しい水着なんだけど　どうかな？
How is it?
ああ…
ヘン？
全然　ヘンじゃないです！
Weird?
No way, totally not!
It looks good on you!  It's beautiful!
似合います！　キレイです
Really?  Thanks.
本当に？　ありがとう
でも　だったら
すぐ褒めてくれたらいいのに
You should've just said so immediately.
I'm sorry, I couldn't stop staring.
すみません　見とれちゃって
そっか　悩殺しちゃったか
I see.  So you were entranced.
さッ　さあ　泳ぎましょう！
W-Well, let's swim!
お先に
I'll go first!
（プールに飛び込む）
Hey, wait for me!
こら～　待ってよ
Isn't going for a swim at the pool on Christmas surprisingly nice?
・（はるか）クリスマスにプールで泳ぐって
いうのも意外にいいでしょう？
I-It's actually pretty fun, but...
確かに　おもしろいですけど…
・（はるか）けど？
But?
やっぱり慣れてないから
違和感がありますね
I'm not used to it, after all.  It feels weird.
・（はるか）そうかな？
ええ
Really?
Yeah.
〈先輩とクリスマスを過ごしてるって
だけでもすごいことなのに〉
It's amazing enough just to be spending Christmas with Senpai.
But swimming together at the pool on top of that... it's unreal.
〈プールで一緒に泳いでるだなんて
現実とは思えないな〉
・（はるか）こら
Hey.
You have me already, so don't look at other girls.
私といるのに
他の女の子　見たりしないの
えッ？
What?
あッ　違いますよ　見てないです！
You got it wrong, I wasn't looking!
と　いうか
目の前に先輩がいるのに
I mean, I already have you in front of me,
so there's no need for me to look at other girls!
他の女の子なんか
見る必要ないです
R-Really?  Okay, then.
そ…　そう？　ならいいけど
ああ…　はい
Okay.
It's hot in here.
〈さあ　さっぱりしたし　次は〉
Yeah.
Wow Tachibana-kun, you're sweating so much!
R-Really?
Yeah.  I mean, look.
You're sweating so much more than I am.
This...
It's incredible enough that our bare skins are touching, but our sweat is also...
Mixing together and dripping onto the floor...
All right, I'm gonna make myself sweat more than you!
Now that I'm all cleaned up, Senpai will finally introduce me to her family.
〈ついに先輩のご家族を
紹介してもらうんだよな〉
〈緊張する〉
I'm nervous.
I'm sorry I took so long to change.
ごめんね
着替えるのに手間取っちゃった
全然平気です　それより
Don't worry about it at all.
More importantly, will we still be
on time to meet up with your family?
ご家族の方達との待ち合わせの
時間は　まだ大丈夫なんですか？
ああ　そっか　忘れてた
Oh, yeah.  I forgot.
You can't forget something like that, Senpai!
忘れちゃダメですよ　先輩
で　待ち合わせの時間って
何時だったんですか？
So when were we supposed to meet up with them?
ああ　一応予定だと１時間前
We planned on meeting an hour ago.
えーッ！
集合場所は　どこなんですか？
Where's the meeting place?
えっとね…　ここ
Let's see...
Here.
え～ッ！
What?!
・（はるか）このホテルの上の階が
待ち合わせ場所なの→
The place where we're supposed to meet up is just upstairs.
だから
そんなに急がなくても大丈夫
So there's no need to rush.
何だ…　って
Right...
Wait.  Even so, we're already an hour late, so we gotta hurry!
それにしても　もう１時間も
遅刻してるんだから急がないと
Wait!
・（はるか）ちょっと！
Geez, you're so pushy.
（はるか）もう…　強引なんだから
ああ　す　すみません
S-Sorry.
うわあ～
どんどん昇っていくね
Whoa, we're going higher and higher!
〈うッ　僕　高所恐怖症なんだよね〉
I have a fear of heights.
〈これは怖すぎる
何か話でもしないと…〉
This is way too scary.  I've gotta start a conversation.
せッ　先輩　今日ってご家族の
どなたがいらしてるんですか？
S-Senpai, who in your family is going to be there?
ああ　うん　実はね
Oh, yeah.  Actually, because of flight delays,
my grandparents weren't able to come today.
飛行機の都合で今日は
おじいちゃん達　来られないの
だから２人っきり
ああ　そうなんですか
We'll be alone together.
I see.
ええッ　２人きり！？
うん　そう
Alone together?!
That's right.
What about your parents?
で　ご両親は
どうしてるんですか？
おじいちゃん達が
来られないんじゃ意味ないって
They said there's no point in going if my
grandparents couldn't make it.  They're at home.
家にいるわよ
ああ　家に…
O-Oh, at home.
でね　せっかく予約してある部屋が
もったいないなと思って
I didn't want to waste the room we already reserved, so I came to spend the night.
泊まりにきたの
確かにもったいない…　ですね
It would be a waste, I guess...
（はるか）残念
夜景　もう少し見てたかったな→
What a shame.
I wanted to look at the night scenery a little longer.
行きましょう
はい
Let's go.
O-Okay.  We're going...
行きますか…
うう…
うわ～！
E-Excuse me.
おじゃまします
あッ
ほらほら　夜景も見えるよ
Look, look.
We can see the night scenery!
Y-Yeah.
えッ　ええ
I wonder what the bathroom's like?
あッ　トイレはどうかな？
S-Senpai?
せッ　先輩
・（はるか）ねえねえ
トイレも立派だよ～
Hey, the bathroom's really great too!
わあ　おふろもおっきい！
すごいよ～
Ooh, the bathtub's really big!
Amazing!
W-Wow.  Amazing.
わ　わあ…　すごいですね
せっかくだから
私　おふろ入っちゃおうかな
Since I'm already here, I think I'll take a bath.
えッ　おふろですか！？
A bath?!
こんな　おっきなおふろ
めったに入れないし
You rarely see a bath this big, so it'd be a waste not to.
もったいないじゃない？
あッ…
そうですね
Y-You're right.
No peeking.
のぞいちゃダメだよ
I-I won't!
のッ　のぞきません！
Wow, good answer.
ワオッ　いいお返事
Well, I'll be taking my bath.
じゃあ　ちょっと入ってくるね
はあ
She's actually taking a bath.
〈本当に
おふろ入りに行っちゃった〉
〈一緒に入った方が　いいのかな？〉
S-Should I go in with her?
〈いや　僕と先輩は
まだ　そんな関係じゃ…〉
No no, we're not close enough for that yet...
Hmm, but I'd like to get that close...
〈ああ　でも
そういう関係になりたいわけで〉
Ugh, what am I thinking about?!
〈て　何を考えてるんだ！〉
（はるかの鼻歌）
〈本当に森島先輩と一緒に
クリスマスイブを過ごせるなんて〉
I can't believe I'm actually spending
Christmas Eve with Morishima-senpai.
〈少し前は考えられなかった〉
I wouldn't have even dreamed of it not too long ago.
〈一度　フラれたときは
つらかったな〉
It was really tough when she turned me down once.
〈でも　くじけないで　もう一度
アタックして本当によかった〉
But I'm glad I didn't give up and went on the offensive again.
〈こうしてイブを
一緒に過ごせるんだから〉
Thanks to that, I'm able to spend Christmas Eve with her.
・（逢）お待たせしました
・（薫）サンキュー→
Here you go.
Thanks.
TL Note: Oden is a winter dish, most closely analogous to stew.
I'm so glad I managed to get Oden from the Swim Club before they sold out!
French Fries
水泳部のおでん
売り切れ前に買えてよかった～
Thank you.
（逢・響）ありがとうございました
French Fries
（逢）一段落しましたね　塚原先輩
Looks like things have settled down, Tsukahara-senpai.
It has.  Nanasaki, you can go home now.
そうね　七咲
あなた　もう帰っていいわよ
弟君が待ってるんでしょ？
Your brother's waiting, isn't he?
ああ　はい
でもまだ片付けが…
Yes, but we still need to clean up-
他の部員とやっておくから
I'll do the cleaning up with the other club members.
じゃあ　ありがとうございます
Then... thank you very much!
ふふ　あの子も頑張ってるかしら？
French Fries
I wonder how she's doing right now.
（詞）うん？
・（詞）ホワイトクリスマスね
A white Christmas, huh?
〈で　これから
どう過ごしたらいいんだ？〉
So how will we spend the time?
〈先輩が　おふろから出たら
僕もおふろに入るのか？〉
Should I take a bath too, after Senpai's done?
〈まあ　確かに入らないと
マズイよな…〉
Well, it'd be bad if I didn't...
〈だから　何でマズイんだよ！〉
TL Note: In Japan, showering/bathing is a prelude to sex.
Wait, why would it be bad?!
That's no different from what you were just thinking about!
〈これは　さっきと同じじゃないか〉
えッ　停電か？
A power outage?
（はるか）違うよ
Nope.
先輩？
Senpai?
（はるか）恥ずかしいから
私が消したの
It's embarrassing, so I turned the lights off.
えッ…
その　かっこうは…
Why are you only in a...
先輩？
Senpai?
バカ
えッ？
Dummy.
どうして
のぞきに来てくれないの？
Why didn't you come and peek at me?
はあ？
どうして　のぞきに来ないのよ！？
Why didn't you come and peek?!
え～ッ！
Crap!  So I was supposed to go and peek!
〈しまった～　僕　のぞきに
行かなきゃいけなかったのか！〉
You don't... like me?
私のこと　好きじゃないの？
すッ　好きですけど
I-I like you.
好きなら　おもわず
のぞいちゃうもんじゃないの？
Wouldn't you peek without hesitation if you really did like me?
Well, I wonder...
いや…　それは　どうですかね
I don't understand.
分からない…
先輩？
Senpai?
どうして
もう一度　告白してくれないの？
Why won't you confess to me again?
何度でも告白するって
言ってくれたのに
Even though you said that you'd
confess as many times as it'd take...
私…　私は君が好きなの！
I...
I like you!
I really do!
大好きなの！
先輩
Senpai.
I've been waiting...
私…　ずっと待ってたのに
I've been waiting all this time...
ずっとずっと　待ってたのに
もう嫌われちゃったかと思って
I thought that maybe you didn't like me anymore...
あきらめられちゃったのかと
思って
I thought that maybe you'd given up...
I was so lonely... and scared...
寂しくて
不安で…
That's not it at all.
そんなことないです
But I don't understand!
でも分からないの
私　こんなに人を好きになったこと
なんてないんだもん
I've never fallen this deeply in love with someone before.
誰にも渡したくない人なんて
初めてなんだもん
It's the first time I've ever wanted to keep someone for myself.
私　どうしたらいいのか
分からなくて
I don't know what to do!
すみません　僕がもっと
ちゃんとできたら　よかったのに
I'm sorry.  I should've done better.
I couldn't even confess properly to you.
Would you still want someone like me?
ちゃんと
告白もできないような僕で
先輩は　いいんですか？
ううん
No, your confession was really great.
君の告白は　とっても素敵だった
２回目の告白のとき
人に告白されて
When you confessed the second time, it was the
first time my heart's ever raced from a confession.
初めてドキドキしたんだから→
でも　だから自分の気持ちを
君にちゃんと伝えるには→
But because of that, I wasn't sure how to let you know how I feel...
どうしたらいいのか
分からなくって→
私の方こそ
ちゃんと告白もできなくって→
I'm the one who can't even confess properly...
I was afraid that you'd give up on me, Tachibana-kun...
橘君に　あきれられちゃうんじゃ
ないかって→
心配で　不安で…
I was worried... and scared...
いいんですよ
It's okay.
えッ？
先輩は　そのままで
You can stay just like this.
僕が好きになった森島先輩は
そういう人だと思います
That's the Morishima-senpai I fell in love with.
I'll get it all right from now on.
今度からは
僕が　ちゃんとしますから
だから　もう泣かないでください
So please don't cry.
Call me "Haruka".
はるかって呼んで
いつまでも　「先輩」じゃイヤ
I don't want you to keep calling me "Senpai".
呼んでくれたら　もう泣かないから
If you call me by my name, I won't cry anymore.
はるか…
Haruka.
よくできました
Well done.
好きだよ
I love you.
ずっとずっと　一緒にいたい
I want to be with you forever.
私も好きよ→
I love you too.
大好き
I really do.
キスして
Kiss me.
そのまま離さないで
And don't let me go.
10 Years Later
・（響）あれから　もう１０年か…
So it's been ten years since then.
あなた達　うまくやってるの？
Are the two of you getting along well?
・（はるか）ええ？
ヤダ　響ったら→
Oh, come on, Hibiki.
We're all lovey-dovey.
私達　ラブラブよ
まあ　あなた達のことだから
変わり者同士
Well, since you're both weirdos,
I figured you guys would get along fine.
うまく　やってるとは思うけどね
（乱暴にドアが開く）
指名手配犯め　お前を逮捕する！
Criminal scum, you're under arrest!
響　あなたは逃げて！
Hibiki, run!
え－っと　橘君
これは毎日やってるの？
Right, Tachibana-kun.
Do you do this every day?
うッ…
ああ　いえ　その
No, well...
たまに　ですね
ごく　たまに
We do that rarely.
Really rarely.
久しぶりですね　塚原先輩
It's been so long, Tsukahara-senpai!
やっぱり　お医者さんって
忙しいんですか？
You must be busy as a doctor, right?
（響）まあ　ほどほどにね
Well, I'm somewhat busy.
それにしても　これで
本当に刑事だっていうんだから
Though, since you're actually a real detective,
I'm worried for Japan's security.
日本の治安は大丈夫なのかしらね
響　純一には日本の平和は
守れないかもしれないけど
Hibiki.  Junichi might not be able to keep Japan safe,
私のことは一生守ってくれるって
約束してくれたのよ
but he promised me he'd keep me safe forever.
はるか～
純一
Haruka.
Junichi.
I love you as much as the number of stars in the sky!
（響）はいはい　ごちそうさま
Okay, thanks for the meal.
I love you too, Junichi!
Haruka.
はるか…
・（はるか）純一
Junichi!
・～
Kawaii sore dake de
かわいいそれだけで
"Cute".  With just that one word
Muchuu de nadetaku naru urunda hitomi
夢中で撫でたくなる潤んだ瞳
I'm in a daze, and I want to rub my teary eyes
Jarete iru toki wa
じゃれている時は
When you were flirting with me
Natsuite iru dake da to
なついているだけだと
You were just being friendly
Omotteta n da
思ってたんだ
At least, that's what I thought
Koi no hajimari nante
恋の始まりなんて
The beginning of a romance
Yohou hazure no tenki mitai
予報外れの天気みたい
is like a missed weather forecast
Ameagari no niji no sora ni te nobasou
雨上がりの虹の空に手伸ばそう
I stretch my hands towards the rainbow-filled sky after the rain
Kimi no tonari wa sunao na
君の隣は素直な
Because when I'm by your side
Kimochi ni nareru kara
気持ちになれるから
I can be honest with myself
Kizuita kimi no koto omou
気付いた君の事想う
I've realized that when I think about you
Jikan wa mune no oku ga konnani takanaru koto
時間は胸の奥がこんなに高鳴る事
My heart starts to pound so much
Kinou yume no naka ni
昨日夢の中に
In my dream last night
Mata kimi ga dete kita
また君が出てきた
You appeared again
Preview
Next episode preview.
All right, the Tanamachi Kaoru arc starts next episode!
Kaoru, don't take things too far.
What are you talking about?
We'll start things off with a bang!
Uh... keep it reasonable.
Well, let's have fun!
Gotcha.
Oh, darling, I know you're actually happy about this.
Don't snuggle against my elbow.
And don't call me darling!
Next episode, "Buddy".
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc: Chapter 1
Buddy
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc: Chapter 1
Buddy
Next Episode
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc: Chapter 1
Buddy
The new story with Kaoru, my
friend since middle school, begins.
Please look forward to it!